# Juncheng ZHOU

Blog:https://blog.4pro.me
GitHub:https://github.com/Vbubblery
Mail:admin@4pro.me
Tel:+33 0761062775

Strong programming skills and logic, Proficiency in JavaScript. Understand Java, C++, Python well. Proficiency in React.js, Next.js Express.js etc.. frameworks. Familiar with basic data structures and algorithms. Experience in full stack development.

Familiar with machine learning and data minig, Understand various machine learning algorithms and models, have own ideal to treat the data. Specialized deep learning, Proficiency in Keras, Tensorflow, Spark. Learning Natural language processing now.

#### Education

2017-2018 MSc, Data & Knowledge;

Télécom ParisTech, Paris, France

2016-2017 MSc, Informatique;

Université Paris-Sud, Paris, France

2011-2015 BSc, Computer Science (Sino-French cooperation);

Hebei University of Technology, Tianjin, China

SUPINFO, Paris, France

# Experience

#### [Internship] Recommendation System 2018.04-2018.10

- Data mining, process data from mongoDB and export it to table.
- Find a way to transform some poperties between to target (0-5 points)
- Deep learning with Keras (Tensorflow) to build the model.
- Node.js call and get the result from model, and then provides to client via API.

#### [Internship] Mobile Application Development 2015.01-2015.05

- Application's button actions define (IOS & Android)
- Layout of the application (IOS & Andorid)
- Algorithms to get the word from dictionary par fuzzy lookup (IOS)

#### [Internship] Full-Stack Development 2014.07-2015.08

- ASP.net site building
- Node.js restful implement
- Node.js and Express.js build site.

## **Technical Experience**

My Site Build my own site to record the life, the Technical, the news and etc and I will

implement AI (NLP) soon. And this site is based on the Node.js, React.js, Next.js,

Express.js, Material-UI ... The DataBase is MongoDB.

**Machine Learn-**

ing

Various Machine Learning projects about the competition of kaggle. For more,

View them on GitHub

Programming Languages

**Javascript(Node.js):** The main programming language. Development experiences with personal website, 2-D video game, Learn Node.js depuis 2013. Now try to unify the Application (IOS,Android) and software(Windows, Linux) with this single language.

**Java SE & JAVA EE:** Frequently used language. Experiences with develop Android application and JSP website.

**Python:** Just for data science part, support various library files of powerful Machine Learning.

**Spark:** for big data, MapReduce and distributed machine learning.

### **Competences**

Statistiques Datamining, Decision tree Regression

ML Visual Recognition, Deep Learning Keras with Tensorflow

Big Data MapReduce with Spark(Scala), Hadoop, Pig

DataBase Oracle, MongoDB, Redis, Neo4J

OS Linux(Centos, debian and Red Hat), Windows, Docker

#### Extra Skills

- Human Languages:
  - Chinese (native speaker)
  - English
  - French